https://www.evergreennutrition.com/terms-of-use

Cart
BotanicalsChinese HerbsHerbal TopicalsHerbsLiquid HerbsMushroomsPowdered HerbsHealth TopicsAllergiesBlood SugarBone StrengthBrain FunctionCandidaCardio/HeartColon CareDetoxDietDigestionEnergyEyeFirst AidHair/Skin/NailsImmuneJoint HealthLibidoLiver SupportMen's HealthMoodPain/InflammationPH BalanceSleep/CalmUrinaryWomen's HealthHomeopathic/Flower EssencesCombination RemediesFlower EssencesSingle Remedies BoironSingle Remedies HylandsTopical RemediesMineralsMulti MineralsSingle MineralsPersonal CareCosmeticsEssential OilsHair CareOral CareSkin CareSportsSupplementsAmino AcidsAntioxidantsChildren'sFish Oil / EFAGlandularGreen Foods/Super FoodsLettered VitaminsLiquid SupplementsMen's MultiPrenatal MultiProbioticsProtein PowdersWomen's MultiShop by Brand
About Us
Our StaffTestimonialsFrequently Asked Questions
About Us > Frequently Asked Questions > Customer Service > Terms of Use
Terms of Use
Last Modified: May 30, 2015
Acceptance of the Terms of UseWelcome to EvergreenNutrition.com (collectively "Evergreen", "we" or "us"). The following terms and conditions, together with the privacy policy and sale policy these "Terms of Use,"
govern your access to and use of EvergreenNutriton.com, (the “Website”)
including any content, functionality and services offered on or through
the Website whether as a guest or a registered user.
Please read these Terms of Use carefully before using our Website. By using the Website, you accept and agree to be bound and abide by these Terms of Use, and
our Privacy Policy, found at
privacy policy, incorporated herein by reference. If you do not agree to these terms of use, your sole remedy is to discontinue use of the website.
This Website is offered and available to users 18 years of age or older
who reside in the United States or any of its territories or
possessions. By using this Website, you represent and warrant that you
are of legal age to form a binding contract with Evergreen and meet all
of the foregoing eligibility requirements. If you are below 18 years of
age you must be supervised by a parent or guardian before using our
site.
Changes to the Terms of UseWe may revise and update these Terms of Use from time to time at our
sole discretion. All changes are effective immediately after posting
them.
Your continued use of the Website following the posting of revised Terms
of Use means that you accept and agree to the changes. Please check
this page from time to time so you are aware of any changes, as they are
binding on you.
Accessing the Website and Account SecurityWe reserve the right to withdraw or amend this Website, and any service
or material we provide on the Website, in our sole discretion without
notice. We will not be liable if for any reason all or any part of the
Website is unavailable at any time or for any period. From time to time,
we may restrict access to some parts of the Website, or the entire
Website, to users, including registered users.
To place an order on our Website, you will be asked to provide certain
registration details and information. It is a condition of your use of
the Website that all the information you provide to the Website is
correct, current, and complete. You agree that all information you
provide to register with this Website or otherwise, is governed by our
Privacy Policy, and you consent to all actions we take with respect to your information consistent with our Privacy Policy.
When registering an account, you will be required to select a password.
You should treat your account name and password as confidential, and you
should not disclose it to any other person or entity. You agree to
notify us immediately of any unauthorized access to or use of your user
name or password or any other breach of security. You should use
particular caution when accessing your account from a public or shared
computer so that others are not able to view or record your password or
other personal information.
We have the right to disable any user name, password or other identifier, any time in our sole discretion for any reason.
Intellectual Property RightsThe Website and its entire contents, features and functionality
(including but not limited to all information, software, text, displays,
images, video and audio, and the design, selection and arrangement
thereof), are owned by Evergreen Nutrition, its licensors or other
providers of such material and are protected by United States and
international copyright, trademark, patent, trade secret and other
intellectual property or proprietary rights laws.
These Terms of Use permit you to use the Website for your personal,
non-commercial use only. You must not reproduce, distribute, modify,
create derivative works of, publicly display, publicly perform,
republish, download, store or transmit any of the material on our
Website, except as to the extent necessary to use the website for its
ordinary purpose. All of the product photographs on our website are
taken in-house and are the property of Evergreen Nutrition. You agree to
not use our images for any purposes without first obtaining written
permission.
If you wish to make any use of material on the Website other than that set out in this section, please address your request to:
contact@evergreennutrition.com.
TrademarksEvergreen Nutrition’s name and logo trademarks of the Evergreen
Nutrition. You must not use such marks without the prior written
permission of the Company. All other names, logos, product and service
names, designs and slogans on this Website are the trademarks of their
respective owners.
Monitoring and Enforcement; TerminationWe reserve the right to terminate or suspend your access to all or part
of the Website for any or no reason, including without limitation, any
violation of these Terms of Use.
We also reserve the right to fully cooperate with any law enforcement
authorities or court order as outlined in our Privacy Policy.
YOU WAIVE
AND HOLD HARMLESS EVERGREEN NUTRITION AND ITS AFFILIATES, LICENSEES,
AND SERVICE PROVIDERS FROM ANY CLAIMS RESULTING FROM ANY ACTION TAKEN
BY, DURING, OR AS A RESULT OF EVERGEEN NUTRITION’S INVESTIGATIONS AND
FROM ANY ACTIONS TAKEN AS A CONSEQUENCE OF INVESTIGATIONS BY LAW
ENFORCEMENT AUTHORITIES.
Reliance on Information PostedThe information presented on or through the Website is made available
solely for general information purposes. We do not warrant the accuracy,
completeness or usefulness of this information. Any reliance you place
on such information is strictly at your own risk. We disclaim all
liability and responsibility arising from any reliance placed on such
materials by you or any other visitor to the Website, or by anyone who
may be informed of any of its contents.
None of the research or evidence presented on our Website is intended as
a substitute for consulting an appropriate healthcare professional.
The statements found on this website have not been evaluated by the Food
and Drug Administration. The products offered here are not intended to
diagnose, treat, cure, or prevent any disease. If you believe that you
may have a disease condition, please consult your healthcare
practitioner before using any dietary supplement.
Although we do our best to keep this website current, always check the
product label for the most up-to-date information since product changes
may not be immediately updated on our website. Feel free to contact us
if you notice any discrepancies. Thank you.
Changes to the WebsiteWe may update the content on this Website from time to time, but its
content is not necessarily complete or up-to-date. Any of the material
on the Website may be out of date at any given time, and while we try to
maintain an accurate and current website, we make no warranties or
guarantees on the accuracy or currentness of information found on our
Website.
Information About You and Your Visits to the WebsiteAll information we collect on this Website is subject to our
Privacy Policy.
By using the Website, you consent to all actions taken by us with
respect to your information in compliance with the Privacy Policy.
Online Purchases and Other Terms and ConditionsAll purchases through our site are governed by our
Order Agreement, which are hereby incorporated into these Terms of Use.
Links from the WebsiteIf the Website contains links to other sites and resources provided by
third parties, these links are provided for your convenience only. This
includes links contained in blogs or social media posts. We have no
control over the contents of those sites or resources, and accept no
responsibility for them or for any loss or damage that may arise from
your use of them. If you decide to access any of the third party
websites linked to this Website, you do so entirely at your own risk and
subject to the terms and conditions of use for such websites.
Geographic RestrictionsThe owner of the Website is based in the state of Oregon in the United
States. We provide this Website for use only by persons located in the
United States. We make no claims that the Website or any of its content
is accessible or appropriate outside of the United States. Access to the
Website may not be legal by certain persons or in certain countries. If
you access the Website from outside the United States, you do so on
your own initiative and are responsible for compliance with local laws.
Disclaimer of WarrantiesWhile we take great efforts to ensure that our systems are up to date
and secure, we cannot and do not guarantee or warrant that our website
will be free of viruses or other destructive code. Ultimately, you are
the best line of defense against such attacks by implementing sufficient
procedures and checkpoints to satisfy your particular requirements for
anti-virus protection and accuracy of data input and output, and for
maintaining a means external to our site for any reconstruction of any
lost data. WE WILL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY LOSS OR DAMAGE CAUSED BY
VIRUSES OR OTHER TECHNOLOGICALLY HARMFUL MATERIAL THAT MAY INFECT YOUR
COMPUTER EQUIPMENT, COMPUTER PROGRAMS, DATA OR OTHER PROPRIETARY
MATERIAL DUE TO YOUR USE OF THE WEBSITE OR ANY SERVICES OR ITEMS
OBTAINED THROUGH THE WEBSITE OR TO YOUR DOWNLOADING OF ANY MATERIAL
POSTED ON IT, OR ON ANY WEBSITE LINKED TO IT.
YOUR USE OF THE WEBSITE, ITS CONTENT AND ANY SERVICES OR ITEMS OBTAINED
THROUGH THE WEBSITE IS AT YOUR OWN RISK. THE WEBSITE, ITS CONTENT AND
ANY SERVICES OR ITEMS OBTAINED THROUGH THE WEBSITE ARE PROVIDED ON AN
"AS IS" AND "AS AVAILABLE" BASIS, WITHOUT ANY WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND,
EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED. NEITHER THE COMPANY NOR ANY PERSON ASSOCIATED
WITH THE COMPANY MAKES ANY WARRANTY OR REPRESENTATION WITH RESPECT TO
THE COMPLETENESS, SECURITY, RELIABILITY, QUALITY, ACCURACY OR
AVAILABILITY OF THE WEBSITE. WITHOUT LIMITING THE FOREGOING, NEITHER THE
COMPANY NOR ANYONE ASSOCIATED WITH THE COMPANY REPRESENTS OR WARRANTS
THAT THE WEBSITE, ITS CONTENT OR ANY SERVICES OR ITEMS OBTAINED THROUGH
THE WEBSITE WILL BE ACCURATE, RELIABLE, ERROR-FREE OR UNINTERRUPTED,
THAT DEFECTS WILL BE CORRECTED, THAT OUR SITE OR THE SERVER THAT MAKES
IT AVAILABLE ARE FREE OF VIRUSES OR OTHER HARMFUL COMPONENTS OR THAT THE
WEBSITE OR ANY SERVICES OR ITEMS OBTAINED THROUGH THE WEBSITE WILL
OTHERWISE MEET YOUR NEEDS OR EXPECTATIONS.
THE COMPANY HEREBY DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, WHETHER EXPRESS
OR IMPLIED, STATUTORY OR OTHERWISE, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO ANY
WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, NON-INFRINGEMENT AND FITNESS FOR
PARTICULAR PURPOSE.
THE FOREGOING DOES NOT AFFECT ANY WARRANTIES WHICH CANNOT BE EXCLUDED OR
LIMITED UNDER APPLICABLE LAW.
Limitation on LiabilityIN NO EVENT WILL THE COMPANY, ITS AFFILIATES OR THEIR LICENSORS, SERVICE
PROVIDERS, EMPLOYEES, AGENTS, OFFICERS OR DIRECTORS BE LIABLE FOR
DAMAGES OF ANY KIND, UNDER ANY LEGAL THEORY, ARISING OUT OF OR IN
CONNECTION WITH YOUR USE, OR INABILITY TO USE, THE WEBSITE, ANY WEBSITES
LINKED TO IT, ANY CONTENT ON THE WEBSITE OR SUCH OTHER WEBSITES OR ANY
SERVICES OR ITEMS OBTAINED THROUGH THE WEBSITE OR SUCH OTHER WEBSITES,
INCLUDING ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL OR
PUNITIVE DAMAGES, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PERSONAL INJURY, PAIN
AND SUFFERING, EMOTIONAL DISTRESS, LOSS OF REVENUE, LOSS OF PROFITS,
LOSS OF BUSINESS OR ANTICIPATED SAVINGS, LOSS OF USE, LOSS OF GOODWILL,
LOSS OF DATA, AND WHETHER CAUSED BY TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE), BREACH
OF CONTRACT OR OTHERWISE, EVEN IF FORESEEABLE.
THE FOREGOING DOES NOT AFFECT ANY LIABILITY WHICH CANNOT BE EXCLUDED OR LIMITED UNDER APPLICABLE LAW.
Governing Law and JurisdictionThis Terms of Use will be governed by and construed in accordance with
the laws of Oregon, excluding its conflicts of laws principles. All
legal proceedings arising from, (a) placing or fulfilling Your order,
(b) your use of the Site, (c) the content of the Site, or (d) the terms
of this agreement, the Terms of Use Agreement, or our Privacy Policy
must be brought in a court of competent jurisdiction in Lane County,
Oregon. All legal claims must be brought within a year after the cause
of action occurs, otherwise the claim is agreed to be barred.
Additionally, you agree to submit to the personal and exclusive jurisdiction of the courts located within Lane County, Oregon.
Limitation on Time to File ClaimsAny cause of action or claim you may have arising out of or relating to
these terms of use or the website must be commenced within one (1) year
after the cause of action accrues, otherwise, such cause of action or
claim is permanently barred.
Waiver and SeverabilityNo waiver of by the Company of any term or condition set forth in these
Terms of Use shall be deemed a further or continuing waiver of such term
or condition or a waiver of any other term or condition, and any
failure of the Company to assert a right or provision under these Terms
of Use shall not constitute a waiver of such right or provision.
If any provision of these Terms of Use is held by a court or other
tribunal of competent jurisdiction to be invalid, illegal or
unenforceable for any reason, such provision shall be eliminated or
limited to the minimum extent such that the remaining provisions of the
Terms of Use will continue in full force and effect.
Entire AgreementThe Terms of Use, our Privacy Policy, and our Order Agreement constitute
the sole and entire agreement between you and Evergreen Nutrition with
respect to the Website and supersede all prior and contemporaneous
understandings, agreements, representations and warranties, both written
and oral, with respect to the Website.
Your Comments and ConcernsThis website is operated by Evergreen Nutrition Inc., an Oregon Coproration.
All other feedback, comments, requests for technical support and other
communications relating to the Website should be directed to:
contact@evergreennutrition.com.
Thank you for visiting the Website.
The information provided here is for educational purposes only. None
of the research or evidence presented here is intended as a substitute
for consulting an appropriate healthcare professional.
These statements have not been evaluated by the Food and Drug
Administration. The products offered here are not intended to diagnose,
treat, cure, or prevent any disease. If you believe that you may have a
disease condition, please consult your healthcare practitioner before
using this or any other dietary supplement.
PLEASE NOTE: WE DO NOT SHIP OUTSIDE OF THE UNITED STATES.
Although we do our best to keep this website current, always check the
product label for the most up-to-date information since product changes
may not be immediately updated on our website. Feel free to contact us
if you notice any discrepancies. Thank you.
